https://www.windhill.com/privacy-policy/

Phone: 603-581-2675 | Email: info@windhill.com
Hit enter to search or ESC to close
Privacy PolicyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.The Information We May Collect:This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on windhill.com. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:NameAddressEmail addressPhone numberThe Way We Use Information:We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive.We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.Our Commitment To Data SecurityTo prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy:Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attractanyone under 13.How You Can Access Or Correct Your InformationYou can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by the provided online tools to do so. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.How To Contact UsShould you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 603-581-2675 or send us an email to websites@windhill.comProviding digital marketing services for small businesses with the goal of delivering results with exceptional service.Important LinksMy AccountPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsAccessibility StatementFeatured ServicesLocal SEOSearch Engine OptimizationWebsite DevelopmentManaged Web HostingContact Us Mailing Address
7227 Pleasant Street Loudon, NH 03307-1615 Phone: 603-581-2675 Email: info@windhill.com ©2020 Windhill Design. All Rights Reserved.
Phone: 603-581-2675 | Email: info@windhill.comAboutBlogContact UsFAQsWordPress Web DesignWordPress DevelopmentE-CommerceWebsite HostingSEOSearch Engine OptimizationLocal SEOSocial Media MarketingPay Per Click ManagementOur WorkCase StudiesPortfolioWebsite SEO AnalysisAbout SalientThe Castle Unit 345 2500 Castle Dr Manhattan, NYT: +216 (0)40 3629 4753 E: hello@themenectar.com
